Okay. So, um it's project time again. Um
this project is going to look shockingly
familiar. Um we are going to make a
weighted GPA calculator. Um so, we are
going to use some of what we did in our
selection project and we're going to
rebuild it this time. So, I want you to
write a program that asks the user for
the number of classes they are taking.
For each class, I want you to ask them
what letter grade they got in the class
and how many credits that class was
worth. So, if the class is worth one
credit, um, then they would say that
class. So, maybe they're taking like
spreadsheets, spreadsheets, one credit.
Maybe they're taking accounting, you'd
say accounting, three credits. I want
you to just gather all of that
information. As you do, um, you're
probably going to want to store that in
an array. Um, I didn't make you here. If
you know a better way to do it, go for
it. Um but um one way you could possibly
do it is to store them in parallel
arrays. Um then I want you to convert
each letter grade to its corresponding
grade point value. So instead of having
an A, I want you to make it a 4.0, an A
minus to be a 3.7, etc. Then I want you
to use the following GPA formula. I want
you to take each grade point and
multiply it by the credits it is. So
like your spreadsheets class, maybe
that's worth one credit. You'd take
whatever you earned, so maybe you're
4.0, and you'd multiply it by one. And
then once you've multiplied each of them
by their weight, I want you to sum them
all up. And then I want you to divide it
by the total number of credits that were
taken.
Um, and then after calculating the GPA
for the semester, display one of the
following messages. And those messages
are there for you. And then down at the
bottom, I've included the grade table.
So, good luck. Um,
and I'll see you in the next